const quiz2data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "__ book here is mine.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "That", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "This", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help:'We use "this" to talk about an object near the speaker.'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "I'm going to return ___ boots I bought last week.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "those", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "these", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help:'We use "those" (plural) for things which are distant from us in time.'
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "- Shall we go to the cinema?",
      question1: "- Yes, __ is a good idea.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "this", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help:'We use "that" to reply to something someone has said.'
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "__ is my friend Sam.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "This", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "That", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use "this" to introduce a person.'
   },
   {
     id: 5,
     question: "Can you pass me ___ books next to you?",
     answersList: [
       {answer: "these", isCorrect: true},
       {answer: "those", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help:'We use "these" (plural) for things which are near the speaker.'
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Who is the woman on ___ picture over there?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "this", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help:'We use "that" to talk about an object far away from the speaker.'
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "I am very busy __ morning.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "this", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help:'We use "this" to talk about something is near to us in time.'
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "No, __ is not right. I disagree with you.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "this", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help:'We use "that" to reply to something someone has said.'
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "You have to throw away ___ boxes over there.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "these", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "those", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help:'We use "those" (plural) to talk about things far away from the speaker.'
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "__ are my friends James and Sam.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "These", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "This", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help:'We use "these" (plural) to introduce people.'
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "__ movie we watched last week was amazing.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "This", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "That", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help:'We use "that" for things which are distant from us in time.'
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "Good morning, __ is Dennis speaking.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "this", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help:'We use "this" to introduce ourselves to someone on the phone.'
    },
  ]
export default quiz2data
